

YURY SHELEST

Junior iOS Developer (Trainee)



Belarus, Minsk



y_shelest@mail.ru



+375 29 960 26 27

LinkedIn:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/yura-shelest

GitHub:

https://github.com/MYAZHA

SUMMARY:

I have a great desire and motivation to start a career in iOS development. Thanks to technical education and past experience, I have the skills of analytical and critical thinking.

I know how to work with a lot of tasks and have good time management skills.

I'm fond of cyclic sports (swimming, cycling and running), I take part in amateur competitions. Reaching my goal despite any difficulties, I like learning something new and develop my skills, both personal and professional.

WORK EXPERIENCE:

Head Project Engineer

LLC "STF-montazh" | Jun 2021 - Current time

- Analytics and control of the department's work.
- Mentoring junior employees.
- Introduction of new technologies and solutions.

Structural Engineer

LLC "STF-montazh" | Feb 2017 - Jun 2021

- Design and construction of products made of aluminum profiles, design of structures of ventilated facades.
- Development of technical solutions and author's supervision.

EDUCATION:

IT ACADEMY | iOS Development:

Mar 2022 - Aug 2022

During the education I got good knowledge of Swift, multithreading, design patterns, OOP, SOLID and MVVM. At work I used:

- Almost all elements of UIKit
- UI by code, by Xib
- CoreData, UserDefaults, FileManager
- Firebase Realtime Database, Storage and Auth
- CocoaPods, Postman, Sourcetree

Streamline | Pre-Intermediate course: 2019 - 2020

Belarusian National Technical University: Bachelor's degree | 2015 - 2018

- Bachelor's degree, «Economics and management»
- Fundamentals of economics and management at industrial enterprises.

Belarusian National Technical University: Bachelor's degree | 2012 - 2017

- Bachelor's degree, «Civil and industrial engineering»
- Design of civil and industrial buildings.
- Construction of various building structures.

MAIN SKILLS:

- Swift
- UlKit, MessageUl, Alamofire, Xib
- Firebase Realtime Database and Storage
- CoreData, UserDefaults, FileManager
- Multithreading, GCD
- CocoaPods, Git
- OOP, SOLID, MVVM
- English A2 (Pre-Intermediate)